COSTA ANTON

Video Game Programmer

@ costa.anton@hotmail.com
• https://antoncosta.github.io/

INTRODUCTION

Hello,

I'm Costa, a video game programmer from Romania, experienced with mobile, desktop and web development. I am an open-minded, hard-working, individual who consistently strives to attain new knowledge and new experiences. Curiosity has always pushed me forward to try new things and I, without fail, have the perseverance to finish what I start. I consider myself to be a fast learner, or, at the very least, persevering enough to learn as quickly as possible. Apart from the education at universities in Romania I have done one semester in Krakow in Poland and 1 year of study in the Netherlands, both part of an ERASMUS scholarship. I have quickly adapted to both countries and have learned a lot from these experiences.

EXPERIENCE

Gameplay Programmer

Tractor Set GO!

• I am currently employed at Tractor Set GO!. The project I am currently working on at the company is an NFT based top-down shooter. It is set in historical time periods and locations (for instance WW2 England) and you are playing as characters from a varied roster based on what you have unlocked. The game is developed in Unity and I am mainly programming gameplay features (combat, abilities, weapons) and occasionally setting-up sounds, animations and effects.

Game Developer for Card Game

Freelance

• This project started as freelance work but at the moment the it's on stand-by. I didn't give its name but I can describe a bit of how it behaves at the moment. It is a browser based collectible card game, meant to be played online, with RPG elements and heavy emphasis on your hero card, the cards in your deck meant to support them. The map is randomly generated, each hex providing different benefits and affecting each class differently. The game is made in Unity using C# and I have used Mirror Networking for the multiplayer element. There are also a couple of shaders made by me using HLSL. The server was deployed on AWS and the client as well. There is a matchmaking system in place and multiple games of two players can be held at the same time.

Solitaire Expert

Freelance

 The game is a variant of the classic solitaire game, made in Unity using C# and a bit of HLSL. I added a lot of functionality and visuals to a game that was in a basic state and I deployed it on the google play store and apple app store.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer ARRK Research & Development

April 2021 - December 2021

 In my probation period I had small introductory Python and Angular projects, some for external clients, some for internal use. After that I have been assigned to ongoing full stack BMW projects. I am working in a team with multiple people and we are using Angular, nestJS and deployment on AWS.

European Economic Area(EEA) Placement Grant

University of Iceland

 A two-month mobility in Iceland to work at the university on a research project. I developed a Virtual Reality application in the Unity game engine to help people that suffer from Acrophobia (fear of heights).

Full time Programmer/Localisation Engineer

Pragmatic Play

 A Unity game engine developer for slots games. My task was to create Unity editor extensions, or to continue existing extensions, to help streamline the game production. I was also part of the localisations team and we were responsible for the maintenance of the application.

Intern

Property Shark

mar 2018 - Sep 2018

A six-month period of internship. One half
 of it working with Visual Basic to do User
 Acceptance Tests. The second half was
 with C# creating and modifying ASP.NET
 applications. Both of them related the
 "PropertyShark - Real Estate Search and
 Property Information " website

EDUCATION

Master's Degree, Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality

University Politehnica of Bucharest

2018 - 2020

♀ Bucharest, Romania

The Master focused on Computer Graphics mostly, OpenGL, C++ and video game engines, video game design and development, as well as a bit of marketing advice. Along with game engine, there was also an emphasis on Virtual Reality, as most university projects related to virtual reality were done by the computer graphics department.

Master's Degree, Computer Graphics

University of Groningen

2019 - 2020

Q Groningen, Netherlands

Part of an ERASMUS+ study exchange. I have continued the master's that I have started in Bucharest on Computer Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality.

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science Babes-Bolyai University

2015 - 2018

♥ Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Web development focused, emphasis on OOP, it's principles and mobile applications as well as website development for mobile environments.

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science AGH University of Science and Technology

2017 - 2017

♥ Kraków, Poland

Exchange student for one semester with ERASMUS+. I mainly did courses in the field of Computer Science which were equivalent with what I would have done back home, one exception being a Polish Language course which was for exchange students.

High School, Mathematics and Informatics National College "Gheorghe Sincai"

2011 - 2015

P Baia Mare, Romania

SKILLS

Unity C#

Mirror Networking

AWS

AR&VR

Unreal

C, C++ Java

Angular

Python

JavaScript

TypeScript

INTERESTS

Technical

- Video Game Programming and Design
- Shaders & Computer Graphics
- Front-end web development
- Back-end web development

Hobbies

- · Playing video games.
- Writing fantasy stories.
- Travelling.
- Listening to audio books.
- Juggling and Magic.

LANGUAGES

English Romanian French Polish Japanese



REFERENCES

Prof. Dr. Ing. Alin Moldoveanu @ alin.moldoveanu@cs.pub.ro

Dr. Jiří Kosinka@ j.kosinka@rug.nl

STRENGTHS

Hard-working Fast learner Curious

Imaginative Adaptable

Game Engines

Video Game Design & Development

Mobile Applications

Web Development